# **Richard Crossley**

## **Quality Inspector**

Steubenville, OH - Email me on Indeed: indeed.com/r/Richard-Crossley/a6fff1c2afdc915c

I'm highly skilled with a record of success in computer troubleshooting, repair, and programming. I'm a creative problem solver with proven ability to detect and resolve IT problems. I also can identify the experience and attributes of others, work collaboratively within a team environment or alone.

- Team Building I have the ability to resolve conflict and improve morale within a team to help drive output for organizational change, execute core competencies, and ensure a valued customer satisfaction.
- Communication Equally strong with interfacing with customers from a variety of different industries and all levels of decision makers up to and including executive levels.
   Authorized to work in the US for any employer

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

#### **Quality Inspector**

Ball Corporation - Weirton, WV - March 2014 to December 2016

Material Distribution

Ensure Bundles are stacked properly for shipment across the country and are free of an defects.

Apex Environmental - January 2014 to March 2014

Air Quality Tech

Supervise surrounding area to be sure that odor was not present for those living in the vicinity of the landfill.

### **Customer Service/Inventory Control**

H & H Graphics - Steubenville, OH - August 2013 to December 2013

Controlled Inventory Levels 

Customer Service

Maintain inventory and organization of all pre-production materials and put together orders for production.

#### Cashier/Cook

Di Carlo's Pizza - October 2012 to September 2013

Cashier Operations 

Cut and Topped Pizza

Responsible for preparing and cooking, cutting, and topping pizza to fulfill customer orders. Also responsible for taking calls and processing transactions for customers.

#### **Pest Control Technician**

Witt Pest Management - Pittsburgh, PA - April 2011 to February 2012

Identify Pest Problems 

Chemically Treat Residential, Commercial, and Industrial Environments

Provide pest control support to residential customers. This includes both indoor and outdoor treatments. Also trained in heat treatments to get rid of bed bugs in homes.

### **EDUCATION**

# Associate Degree in Software Engineering in Software Engineering

West Virginia Northern Community College 2016 to 2017

# **Certificate in Development Programming**

West Virginia Northern Community College 2012 to 2013

# **High School Diploma**

Steubenville High School 2000 to 2004

### **SKILLS**

Android (Less than 1 year), CSS (Less than 1 year), Excel (Less than 1 year), HTML (Less than 1 year), Java (Less than 1 year)

### ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

**SKILLS** 

PHP, JQuery, Java, HTML, CSS, Microsoft Access, SQL, Microsoft Excel, Microsoft Word, Microsoft Powerpoint, Microsoft Visual Basic, Android Mobile App Development